http://www.adcu.com.au/privacy

I Want To
I want to...
Whatever it is you want to do, we're here to help. Read our tips and see how you can get closer to your goals!
Discover
I Want ToBecome a MemberBuild my SavingsBuy a CarBuy a HouseInsure my BelongingsInvest in PropertyLeave the DefenceManage my MoneyPlan for DeploymentPlan for RetirementReduce my FeesRefinance my Home LoanRenovate my HouseTake a Holiday
Products
Products
Browse through our products.
Our products are low cost, great value and packed full of extras.
Discover
ProductsDHOAS Home LoansHome LoansInvestment Home LoansCredit CardPersonal & Car LoansEveryday AccountsSavings AccountsTerm DepositsInsuranceSuperannuationCash PassportOverseas Payments
Tools
Tools
Use our handy Tools
We strive from helping our members. Check out our handy range of interactive tools and see how they can help you.
Discover
ToolsBroker Portal LoginCalculatorsRatesContact UsFind a BranchFind an ATMFormsFinancial HardshipFAQsMobile Banking AppOpen Banking
About
About
Learn more about us
We've been banking with the Defence community since 1959, that makes us Australia's longest serving Defence financial institution.
Discover
AboutContact UsCommunityDisclosure DocumentsGovernanceOur StoryMembershipMobile BankersNewsNewslettersReferral PartnersCareers
ONLINE BANKING
Contact
ATMs
Branches
Rates
Calculators
FAQs
BSB 642 170
Privacy
We’re committed to ensuring the privacy of your personal information.
Home > Privacy
Privacy
We're committed to the privacy of our members
Our Privacy Policy outlines how we deal with your personal information (including credit-related information), as well as our legal obligations and rights as to that information. It covers:
The types of personal information we collect and how we collect this information
How we use your information
Who we disclose your information to
How we keep your information secure
How you can access and correct your personal information
How you can make a privacy complaint
How to contact us to find out more
Download our Privacy Policy
For more information on credit reporting, we recommend that you visit http://www.creditsmart.org.au which provides a helpful overview of the effects of the Privacy Act reforms on how credit reporting operates in Australia.
Contact Us
"Australian Military Bank have looked after all my banking needs since 1999. I am Australian Military Bank through and through."
Australian Military Bank Ltd ABN 48 087 649 741 AFSL and Australian Credit Licence Number 237 988.
Your browser is out-of-date!
click here to access online banking
click here to upgrade your browser
×
